Guide to the Helen Bullard papers, 1920-1950.
Bullard, Helen papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Helen Bullard papers, 1920-1950.
6501
Bullard
8 cubic ft.
Correspondence, publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The collection contains original files of H.E. Bullard containing both personal correspondence and memorabilia (music programs, tax records, and Sunday school materials) and professional project papers and blueprints.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Landscape architect, city planner. Helen Elise Bullard, was born in Schuylerville, New York on June 28, 1896, the daughter of Dr. Thomas E. Bullard and Elizabeth Huggins Bullard. She attended the Schuylerville Public School. She graduated from Cornell University with a Bachelor in Science Degree in Landscape Architecture (then Landscape Art) from the College of Agriculture. She was employed by the Wagner Park Nursery Company at Sidney, Ohio (not verified) where she lectured and advised on Small Home Grounds. From 1921 to 1925 she worked in the office of Warren H. Manning, Boston, Massachusetts as the plantsman and planting designer and supervisor of projects. She worked on both private estates and community pageants. By 1929 she was employed in the office of Annette Hoyt Flanders and supervised a number of estate projects, primarily on Long Island. In 1930 she was employed by the New York State government. She began in the Civil service, performing projects for the Long Island State Park Commission, Rye Beach Park, and the Southern State Parkway. In 1937 she was assigned as a Landscape Architect for the New York World's Fair, 1939. She was named Junior Landscape Architect for the New York State Department of Public Works in 1938 and remained there until she retired in 1964. During her career she lectured on gardening, garden design, city planning, and housing issues. She died in Schuylerville, New York on November 4, 1987.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The collection contains original files of H.E. Bullard containing both personal correspondence and memorabilia (music programs, tax records, and Sunday school materials) and professional project papers and blueprints. These papers include: journals from her courses at Cornell University from 1915 to 1918; blueprints and correspondence related to her work in the offices of Warren H. Manning (1921-1925) and Annette Hoyt Flanders (1929); an extensive collection of clippings from contemporary professional and lay magazines and journals as well as travel brochures from the western United States and the Paris Expo 1937; documents from her work as Landscape Designer at the New York State World's Fair, 1939; lecture notes on city planning, housing, garden design, and victory gardens; drawings from projects including work with the C.C.C. on parkways.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Bullard, Helen.; Manning, Warren H.(Warren Henry), 1869-1938.; Cornell University--Students.; New York (State).Long Island State Park Commission.; New York World's Fair
Subjects:
Landscape architecture--United States.; Women landscape architects.
Places:
United States--Description and travel.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Personal
Boxes: 1, 6
Series II. Cornell University education and alumni activities
Boxes: 2, 3
Series III. Professional projects, 1919-1970
Boxes: 3, 4, 6
Series IV. Clippings, 1919-1952, 1964
Boxes: 4, 5, 6
Series V. Travel, 1924-1952
Box: 5
Series VI. Oversize blueprints and drawings, 1922-1963
Boxes?: 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Personal, 1909-1971
  - Undated school notes, No date (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Undated school notes, No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - High school journals/ Composition Book (1909); personal letter to brother? (1910), 1909-1910 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - School notes, Botany course, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ithaca Journal, November 11, 1918, announcement of the end of WWI., 1918 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Bullard to R. Wheelwright, University of Pennsylvania about educational possibilities, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Structural Mechanics course, 1939-1940, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Auto Mechanics course, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Misc. items found in box with calendars and other personal matters: Appalachian Mountain Club membership cards (1925-1926); Town Club of St. Louis Directory (1923); christmas card (1939); hardware receipt (1962); misc. papers; and 3 drafting templates, 1925-1962 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alpha Xi Delta Convention, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Commencement Exercises for Schuylerville High School (1946); Cornell Plantations Bulletins (1944 and 1945)., 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Calendars: 1940, 43,44,45,46,47,48,50,61 (personal calendar with dates and notes), 1940-1961 (Box 1, Folder 12a-j)
  - Calendars: 1953, 54, 57, 59 (personal calendars with dates and notes), 1953-1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence with Winterthur Museum (related to visit), 1953 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - The Schuylerville Standard, May 19, 1960, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Music Programs: Hippodrome (1911); Carnegie Hall (1929); Fantasia (1940), 1911, 1929, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Music Programs: First Church in Albany, Rochester Philharmonic Orchestra, Leopold Stokowski at the Palace Theatre in Albany, and other programs, 1930-1947 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Music Programs: Albany Symphony Orchestra (1941); Mendelssohn Club of Albany (1940-1953), 1940-1953 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Programs: Albany Institute of History and Art, 1942-1952 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Undated school notes, No date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Misc. Programs: church services, 1941-1950 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Sunday School teaching supplies, 1944-1947 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Income Tax forms and receipts for 1965, 1967 – 1969, 1965-1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Income Tax forms and receipts for 1970 and 1971, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Obituary written by nephew, David Bullard; article about her in the New York Sun, 1937- copy, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence Course on Salesmanship (1st of two folders), 1921 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence Course on Salesmanship (2nd of two folders), 1921 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Series II. Cornell University education and alumni activities, 1915-1954
  - Watercolor and pencil drawings (mixed in with school and professional papers), No dates (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Cornell University journals: General Biology Course, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cornell University journals: Geometry Course, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Cornell University journals: General Biology Course, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Cornell University journals: Landscape Art I, examinations and notes, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Cornell University journals: Natural History of The Farm, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence with W. Manning about paper (Manning was a frequent lecturer at Cornell, letter found amongst notes for 1916 Farm Course), No date (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Cornell University journals: Landscape Art, History of Design, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Cornell University journals: Inorganic Chemistry, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Cornell University journals: Botany, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Cornell University journals: Botany, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cornell University journals: Botany I, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Cornell University journals: Landscape Art, plant course, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Cornell University journals: notebook with notes on geology, literature, architecture, 1915-1916 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Notebook (Found with Cornell journals), architectural sketches and other drawings in lead and colored pencil., 1917 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Notebook: personal journal, while at Cornell University, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Cornell University journals: Plant Physiology, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Cornell University journals: Botany (includes pencil sketches), 1917 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Notebook: notes with Cornell University journals: plant lists, landscape construction, housing, game areas, miscellaneous notes, No date (Box 2, Folder 19a)
  - Notebook: notes with Cornell University journals: plant cards, notes, small pieces of paper with notes, No date (Box 2, Folder 19b)
  - Cornell University journals: Plant Physiology, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Cornell University journals: Chemistry, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Cornell University journals: Botany and Floriculture, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Cornell University journals: Botany 20, Spring, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Cornell University journals: Botany 20, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Cornell University journals: Floriculture, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Cornell University journals: Floriculture, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Cornell University journals: Landscape Art, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Cornell University journals: Landscape Art, includes notes on design and city planning, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Cornell University journals: Landscape Art, junior and senior projects including notes on city planning, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Cornell University journals: Landscape Art with R. Curtis, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Cornell University journals: History of Architecture, Rural Engineering, Plant Path. Speechmaking, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Cornell University journals: Plant Pathology, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Cornell University journals: Plant Pathology I, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Cornell University journals: Plant Pathology I, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Cornell University journals: Plant Pathology I, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Cornell University journals: Plant Pathology I, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Cornell University journals: Plant Pathology I, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Cornell University journals: Plant Pathology I, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Women’s Review (Dec. 1916 to June 1917) includes articles on Senior Pageant for Class of 1917, 1916-1917 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Cornell University Alumni package, correspondence, 1925 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Cornell University memorabilia: Cornell vs. Pennsylvania Football program cover (1916); Cornell vs. Dartmouth Football program (missing cover) (1941):Anabel Taylor Hall, Cornell University Program (1952); Invitation to The Cornell Women’s Club of New York 56th Annual Luncheon (1953), 1916, 1941, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Presentation for Cornell Freshman send-off, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Widow, Vol. 1, Issue 1, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Series III. Professional projects, 1919-1970, 1915-1954
  - Small home grounds- notes for lectures and presentations?, 1919? (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - C and H Park, expense sheet, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Warren Manning Office, notes, photographs, correspondence, 1921-1925 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Warren Manning and H.E. Bullard correspondence, 1922-1924 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Calumet Community Pageant, project in Manning Office. References to McCormick garden., 1922 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Willard Clapp project, in Manning office (McCormick garden plan included), 1923 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Oak Hill Cemetery and Clapp correspondence, 1924 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Plant lists provided by Manning Office, 1923 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Springfield City Plan, publications, (map in drawer), 1923 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - H.E. Bullard and Annette Hoyt Flanders, correspondence regarding office and design work for clients, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - H.E. Bullard and Annette Hoyt Flanders, correspondence regarding Kiser Estate, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - H.E. Bullard and Annette Hoyt Flanders, correspondence regarding Simmonds Estate, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Department of Public works, specifications for landscape work for the New York State Psychiatric Institute and Hospital, New York City,(1930); State Office Building (1930); Kings Park State Hospital (1930), 1930 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Department of Public works, specifications for landscape work for the New York State, New State School, Newark, NY; Brooklyn State Hospital, Long Island, NY; State Office Building: Instructions for Planting and ‘Care of Trees, Shrubs, ETC, Division of Architecture, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Long Island State Park: contract documents, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - New York World’s Fair, 1939: contracts and tree planting specifications, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - New York World’s Fair, 1939: notes on lecture given in 1939? As Landscape Designer, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - New York State Tourist Information (initially appears to have been collected in preparation for the World Fair), 1939-1939 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - New York World’s Fair, 1939: articles and clippings, 1939-1949 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - New York World’s Fair, 1939: notes on lecture given in 1949, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Construction contracts for NYWF, 1939: specifications for tree planting and supplement, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Construction contracts for NYWF, 1939: specifications for tree planting two documents), 1937 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Construction contracts for NYWF, 1939: specifications for bedding plants and tree planting (two documents), 1938 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Construction contracts for NYWF, 1939: specifications for landscaping and tree planting (three documents), 1938 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Roadside development guide, West Virginia, publication, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Department of Public Works planting specifications for Indian School, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - War Department: specifications for planting of trees (1943); Turf (1943), 1943 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence and misc. estimates: New York State Normal School expenses (n.d.); Executive Mansion specifications and correspondence (1941-42); Rhoads General Hospital map and correspondence (1945)., 1941-1945 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Department of Public Works: specifications for planting of Infirmary Building, Central Islip (two documents), 1944 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - New York State Map and Key, published, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Department of Public Works: specification for landscape work, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Knox Headquarters: field data, report and correspondence, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence C. White, NY State Architect and other experts regarding standardized plant names. Correspondents include Richard P. White, American Nurserymen; Donald Wyman, Arnold Arboretum; William J. Robbins, The New York Botanical Garden; Harlan P. Kelsey, American Joint Committee on Horticultural Nomenclature, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - C.J. Herlihy project correspondence (note sketch on trace paper is in Bullard drawer), 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Specifications and contract for G. C. Bebb, Landscape Architect (appears to have worked in office of NY State Architect, C. White), No date (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Handwritten notes by Bullard on housing issues, appears to be from lectures and readings by H. Wright, C. Bauer, and others., 1934-1940 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence with Carl A. Sorg, Federal Works Agency and copy of his lecture of 1939-1940 on Management of Grounds of Public Housing Projects, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Notes for lecture on garden design, No date (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Notes for lecture on garden design with slides (slides missing), No date (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Notes on lecture on city planning, Albany, New York, No date (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Notes on lecture on housing, No date (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence from G. Clark (Cornell University) to H. Bullard enclosing copy of his lecture on the History of Landscape Architecture, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Clippings and lecture notes on Victory Garden efforts, 1940s (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - American Society of Landscape Architects (ASLA) meetings in 1941, 43, 46, 47: invitations, agendas, and officer lists, 1941-1947 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - ASLA meeting notes and guide to Virginia Garden Week, photographs and postcards., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - ASLA New York Chapter meeting: handwritten notes and financial report, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - ASLA New York Chapter meeting: committee reports and agendas, newsletter and bulletin, membership application, notes on fee structure for professional services, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence with ASLA about a requested change in the directory (original request not found), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Institutional Planning- photographs of hospitals and other misc. institutions. Clipping on Staten Island Hospital, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Souvenirs from parties and events of the State Architect’s Office, Albany, New York, 1941-1948 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - ASLA New York Chapter Exhibit catalogues, 1929, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Housing publications and guides, 1938-1940 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Series IV. Clippings, 1919-1952, 1964, 1915-1954
  - Indexes for Landscape Architecture, A Quarterly Magazine, 1923-1933 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Books lists and advertisements: include announcements for books by F.B. Robinson, U.P. Hedrick, and others as well as clippings of book titles and abstracts. Subjects include gardening, city planning, rendering, China, and general reference books, 1925-1940 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Clippings on beaches in Switzerland, NY City, Cape Cod, article on Olive Tjaden’s (Cornell Alumna?) design for Inwood Beach Club in Atlantic Beach, NJ, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Clippings on and images of bridges including two part article on bridges of ancient china, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Clippings on construction details, expenses, and specifications including an article on Parks in Pittsburgh, 1929-1940 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Construction manuals/ reprints from Landscape Architecture Magazine: cost data notes, Landscape construction estimates, topographic surveys, 1922-1923 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Construction manuals/ reprints from Landscape Architecture Magazine: construction of polo fields, roads for private estates, construction of labor camps, construction of retaining walls, pools, bowling greens, steps and ramps, 1922-1925 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Data sheets (primarily from Pencil Points), estimates and expense sheets, 1933-1937 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Estimates and construction costs, typed sheets, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Clippings of images and articles on drafting a “Handbook of Map Symbols” (1944), 1931-1944 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on drawing, etchers, lithographers, and modern painting, 1929-1940 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on crayon drawings, primarily from Pencil Point, 1930-1933 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on ink drawings, primarily from Pencil Point, 1928-1933 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on pencil drawings, primarily from Pencil Point, some in color, 1929-1937 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on pencil drawings, primarily from Pencil Point, 1930-1933 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on perspective drawings, primarily from Pencil Point, 1929, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Samples from Pencil Point of Lettering, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on mural painting, primarily from Pencil Point, 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on rendering primarily from Pencil Point, 1930-1938 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on watercolors, primarily from Pencil Point, 1930-1937 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on sculpture, primarily from Pencil Point, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Garden pamphlets: “Living Memorials” (n.d.) by Bailey; “The Role of the Garden Club in City Beautification” (1964), 1964, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Nursery Catalogues: Cedar Hill Nursery (1937); Sherwood (1941); Wayside (1944); Mayfair (n.d); Slocum Water Gardens (n.d); misc. clippings (n.d), 1937-1944 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on garden accessories including bird baths, furniture, tools,…, 1929-1938 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on Garden Pools, 1937-1941 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on Greenhouse plants, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on horticultural practices: pruning, trimming, seeding, soil, 1929-1952 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on horticultural practices as published in Horticulture Magazine, 1927-1938 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on horticulture: bulbs, 1928-1940 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on horticulture: irises, 1930, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on horticulture: perennials, 1929-1946 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on horticulture: roses, 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on horticulture: shrubs, 1929-1940 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on horticulture: vegetable gardening, 1919-1944 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on horticulture: wildflowers and native plants, 1939, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on conservation and forestry issues, 1948-1958 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on lawns and turf, 1942-1962 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Clippings of images of and articles on trees, 1926-1953 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Description of Tree Types/ Graphic Standards: folder 1 of 3, No Date (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Description of Tree Types/ Graphic Standards: folder 2 of 3, No Date (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Description of Tree Types/ Graphic Standards: folder 3 of 3, No Date (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Specifications for planting, furnishing, and maintaining trees, including specifications for State Education Building in Albany, NY, primarily typed sheets with HB initials at bottom left corner, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Clippings of articles on and images of architecture, 1919-1942 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Clippings of articles on and images of city planning issues, 1924-1933 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Clippings of articles on and images of housing issues, primarily focused on New York state, 1935-1940 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Clippings of articles on and images of horticultural practices: watering, seeding, soil, 1919-1940 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Clippings of articles on and images of annuals, herbs, 1929-1949 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Clippings of garden calendars and tips on low maintenance gardening, No dates (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Clippings of articles on and images of interior designs, 1919-1929 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Clippings of articles on and images of interior design issues: plumbing, electrical, etc., 1919-1920 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Clippings of articles on and images of garden design issues, 1928-1952 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Clippings of articles on and images of landscape architecture including articles on parks, women and camping in parks (1919), 1919-1947 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Series V. Travel, 1924-1952, 1915-1954
  - Travel to West via New Orleans, Arizona,: tourist information, postcards, and personal notes and telegram, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Travel to California: tourist information, maps, postcards, and photographs. Includes program for performance of THE MISSION PLAY., 1924 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Paris Expo 1937, picture guide, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Greyhound Bus travel to Colorado, Montana, California, Oregon, Idaho, Washington. Utah: tourist information, maps, postcards, and photographs. Includes ticket to Gold Gate Expo, 1939., 1939 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - ASLA Meeting in Detroit, guides to Edison Institute, Greenfield Village, and Cranbrook Institute, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Travel to New England (Mass, Vermont, New Hampshire, Maine, Rhode Island): tourist information, maps, photographs, postcards, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 25)